(Howard:)Boy, oh, boy,
that's a lot of pieces.
(Penny:)You know
what they all do, right?
(Howard:)Yes, of course.
(Sheldon:)What about this one?
(Leonard:)Well, I...
how familiar are you
(Howard:)with miniaturized
integrated logic circuits?
(Sheldon:)Not very.
(Howard:)That right there
is a miniaturized
(Howard:)integrated logic circuit.
(Sheldon:)So, can you
get it working?
(Howard:)I'm an MIT-trained engineer.
(Howard:)I've built components
for the space station.
(Sheldon:)I thought the zero-gravity
toilet didn't work.
(Howard:)It worked fine,
(Howard:)it just wasn't designed
for Russian cosmonauts
(Howard:)and their potato-based diet.
(Raj:)Hey, guys.
(Raj:)Hey.
Hello.
(Raj:)I have to return the helicopter.
My father...
What did you do?!
(Sheldon:)Well, don't worry.
(Sheldon:)He went to MIT.
(Sheldon:)He can solve any problem,
(Sheldon:)as long as it doesn't originate
in a Russian man's colon.